Ae Dil Dhakad Overload Part-2 So if you have
n't subscribed then subscribe
press the bell icon and comment tractor
then this comedy stars ride we viva hai
world of interesting and doors and
its moral support comedy se tyranny
start with forest forest guard is gas
the fee whoever knows the answer will raise his hands and legs
okay the one who raises his hands first
I will ask him did not reply
directly Abhijeet see instructions for
you is wealth of India a little I said
first or yes okay Biswa Biswa this is
left side service and Greater Noida on
or if you have noticed then some face is
formed in front team this match and edition 1999 used to be
good to Niti's Gautam Niti
Dyer Vyan Dyer taw
[laughs]
Bluetooth is on in between Ginger is free
brother and lastly who is my Gas Singh and
Gaurav Gupta such good teeth that I have this photo at the
back the most result Prayal and always others
' hunter but in which he is very soft and
that you even the second one is [ __ ]  That's why I
keep you because Raavan we have to drag it for 15 minutes so that's why
I keep the nose part
small hmm hmm
account big bahut doob Veer Das this was that ah
that Madhur this seems to me very busy ghrm ghrm ghrm ghrm
he wants to see is
not right Silverman appointed also
this a
bhanwari entry will be guys Abhi and found one discover
Vishwas and finally Bigg Boss gets into
yes certificate friend
remedies six hundred and Abhijeet and
central point for president office one by
himself while being highly
subsidized he mentions this is zikr abhi tak khata
nahi khola unfortunately not mentioned and this who is
the little effect Dinesh Jangid is Veer
* enter change language and telly jokes and
quotes by famous ki millions and you have to guess that that
court or which comedian's
but change the background change the language which is
winner change language lab lab na because you
told me that then you will do it
[laughs]
Abhijeet  Open
Hyderabad is right that is Zakir Khan Rahul
Ajit festival Mr 108 Zakir Zakir Khan just
dancer Abhishek Abhishek's finals are
maintaining longevity Allahabad discussion Viva
I singh - 1000 points for both and
electronic products blessings of both of them
[laughs]
you hate people more and more
because it is
very ah
think how stupid a person is now I
realise that most of them are stupid this
vegetable ah here the one who does not speak Kale would be
English dancers danced with 80 my
god gas who is the joke on
this festival
sugar Meena and on the phone Naveen Naveen
loot-loot
loot Naveen Vishwas heart globally
recognized Abhishek Abhishek full-full is
ko fun told notification what is
last name calling Naveen Ghagra Abhishek Naveen
Prabhakar even walking cannot become constipation
you should never keep the sign of walking is temporarily bad
walking is straight temporarily for
convenience the right answer is the this is
for you I did 8 minutes  This was a
trick
that this is a video of a Pakistani friend, you are
new to this, yes yes
but that is the comedian's line, put it like this
or subscribe
that arises where scores right now be
divided into two hundred Abhijeet it is z61 this
letter cafe zombie is a last man acting now
last last and I also don't know the answer to this
and tell me a
man picked up okay friend last sister Sushila
poor then you will put deposit give answer
Abhijeet one loop wise khotwa so who
said it first which should not be done tell me
what did you say this point by rule which was going to
make the least points na will
get the new film Lootera now Abhilash
I want to bring in the last Vilas container
I want Neeti and Abhishek to wash
Yasmin's moment by moment it is fun Abhijeet
more point and second time trying to be needed
help u please do it